A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, International Program in Health Care Policy (IHP), SG 3, Series 14 FA1475
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International Program in Health Care Policy (IHP), 1925-2006; 14
  - Ian Axford (New Zealand) Fellowships in Public Policy, 7
    - Ian Axford (New Zealand) Fellowships in Public Policy - Candidate's Pack, 1997; 1999 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - 1995 Ian Axford (New Zealand) Fellowships in Public Policy (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - 1999 Ian Axford (New Zealand) Fellowships in Public Policy - Application Pack (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - 1999 Ian Axford (New Zealand) Fellowships in Public Policy - Orientation Materials, 1997-1999 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - 2001 Ian Axford Fellowships - Applications and Selection (Box 134)
    - 1999 Ian Axford Fellowships - Applicants (Box 135)
    - 2000 Ian Aford Fellowships - Applicants (Box 135)
    - 2000 Ian Aford Fellowships - Applicants (Box 136)
    - 2001 Ian Aford Fellowships - Applicants (Box 136)
    - 2001 Ian Aford Fellowships - Applicants (Box 137)
    - 1999 Ian Axford (NZ) Fellowships - Application Pack (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - 1999 Ian Axford (NZ) Fellowships - Nominator Letters, 1998 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - 1997-1998 Ian Axford Fellows - Contact List (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - 2002 Ian Axford Fellowships - Nominator Letters, 2000 (Box 138, Folder 4-7)
    - 2002 Ian Axford Fellowships - Nominator Letters, 2000 (Box 139, Folder 1-2)
    - Ian Axford Fellowships - Handbook, 1998 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - 1998 Ian Axford Application Material (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - 1998 Ian Axford Fellowships - New Zealand Embassy Reception (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - 1998 Ian Axford Fellowships - New Zealand Embassy Reception - Invitation Lists (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - 1999 Ian Axford Fellowships - Applicant-Fellow Data, 1998-1999 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - 1999 Ian Axford Fellowships - Nominator List, 1998-1999 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - 1999 Ian Axford Fellowships - New Zealand Embassy Reception, 1998-1999 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Ian Axford Selection Committee - 1999 Cycle, 1998-1999 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - 1999 Ian Axford Fellowships - Marketing, 1998-1999 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - 2000 Ian Aford Fellowships - Nominator List, 1999-2000 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - 2000 Ian Axford Fellowships - Brochure, 1999-2000 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - 2000 Ian Axford Fellowships - New Zealand Embassy Reception, 1999-2000 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - 2000 Ian Axford Selection Committee, 1999 May 8 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Ian Axford Fellowships - Papers, 1999-2000 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Ian Axford Fellowships - Changing Skills for a Changing World, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - 2002 Ian Axford Fellowships - Marketing (Box 191, Folder 2-3)
    - Ian Axford Fellowships - Financial Statements, 1995-1997; 1998-1999 (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - 2001 Ian Axford Fellowships - Marketing (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - 1999 Ian Axford Fellowships - Jenny Gill Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - 1999 Ian Axford Fellowships - Staff Correspondence, 1998 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Ian Axford Fellowships - Board Meeting, 1998 December 11 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - 1999 Ian Axford Fellowships - Karen Davis Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Ian Axford Fellowships - Financial Statements, 1999 October-2000 September (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - 2001 Ian Axford Fellowships - Application, 2000 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - 2001 Ian Axford Fellowships - Board Meeting, 1999 December 10 (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - Fund Sponsorship of USAID Meeting, 2006 (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - 2001 New Zealand Embassy Reception (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - 1997-1998 Ian Axford Fellowships - Budget, 1996-1998 (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - 2002 Ian Axford Fellowships - Selection Committee Meeting, 2001 May 12 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - 2001 Ian Axford Fellowships - Selection Committee Meeting (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Ian Axford Fellowships - Board of Trustees, 1997 December (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - James Pratt, Cornell University (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - New Zealand Harkness - Ian Axford Fundraising, 2000-2001 (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - 1999 Ian Axford Fellowships - George Troup Correspondence, 1997 (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - 1999 Ian Axford Fellowships - James Craig Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 194, Folder 8)
  - Atlantic Fellowships, 8
    - 1998 Atlantic Fellowships - Handbook for Atlantic Fellows (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Atlantic Fellowships, 1997-1999 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 1999 Atlantic Fellowships - General Correspondence, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Atlantic Fellowships - Budget Materials, 1997-1999 (Box 81, Folder 3-4)
    - Atlantic Fellowships - London Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 1998 Atlantic Fellowships - 1998 Orientation (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 1998 Atlantic Fellowships - General Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 1998 Atlantic Fellowships - London Orientation (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 1998 Atlantic Fellowships - Selection Committee, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 1998 Atlantic Fellowships - Background Material, 1994-1997 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - 1998 Atlantic Fellowships - Correspondence (Box 82, Folder 2-3)
    - 1998 Atlantic Fellowships - The Public Management Foundation - Greg Parston (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - 1998-1999 Atlantic Fellowships - Contract (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Atlantic Fellowships - 2001 Selection, 2001 March 16-17 (Box 92, Folder 6-7)
    - Atlantic Fellowships - Papers, 1996-1998 (Box 109, Folder 1-3)
    - Atlantic Fellowships - 1997-1998 Fiscal Report (Box 130, Folder 3-4)
    - Atlantic Fellowships - 1998 Orientation Meeting, New York, NY, 1998 March 20 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - 1999 Atlantic Fellows - Budget (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - 1997-1998 Atlantic Fellows - Applicants (Box 131)
    - 1999 Atlantic Fellows - Selection Committee (Box 131)
    - 1999 Atlantic Fellows - Interviews (Box 131)
    - 2000 Atlantic Fellows - British Consul Correspondence (Box 131)
    - 1998-1999 Atlantic Fellowships - Applicants (Box 137)
    - 1999 Atlantic Fellowships - Applicants (Box 137)
    - 1995 Atlantic Fellowships - Applicants (Box 137)
    - 1999 Atlantic Fellowships - Nominator Letters, 1998 (Box 139, Folder 3-5)
    - 1999 Atlantic Fellowships - Nominator Letters, 1998 (Box 140, Folder 1-6)
    - 2000 Atlantic Fellowships - Applicants, 1999-2000 (Box 141)
    - 1996 Atlantic Fellowships - Handbook and Directory (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Atlantic Fellowships Financial Information, 1998 April-1999 March (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - 1999 Atlantic Fellowships Proposal to Foreign and Commonwealth Office (FCO) (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - 2000 Atlantic Fellowships - New Fellows (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Atlantic Fellowships - Origin and Information, 1994-1995 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Atlantic Fellowships - Financials, 1997-1998 (Box 179, Folder 1-2)
  - IHP Program Files, 9
    - IHP Coordinating Committee Meeting, 1998 February 16 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Program Monitoring Committee Meeting, 2004 September 9 (Box 168, Folder 1-2)
    - 1999-2000 IHP Program Plan (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - 2000 IHP Program Plan (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - 2001 IHP Program Plan (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - 2002 IHP Program Plan (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - 2006 Picker Institute - Review of Professional Codes and Standards for Doctors in the UK, US and Canada, 2006 March (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - IHP Audiovisual Materials, 10
    General
    Audio tape "International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Wednesday - Tape 1" was not included in acquisition and is presumed missing.
    Sound recordings; Moving Images
    - Allistair Cooke - Letter from America: The Early Years, 1946-1968, 1993; Sound, 170 minutes; 1/4 inch audiocassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15143)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please see a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - The Commonwealth Fund - 80th Anniversary Video, 1998 November 9; Sound, 14 minutes13:51; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11738)
    - BBC Horizon: AIDS - Behind Closed Doors (Mark Poznansky, Harkness Fellows 1989-1991), circa 1996; PAL Standard; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11739)
    - BBC Horizon: AIDS - Behind Closed Doors (Mark Poznansky, Harkness Fellows 1989-1991), circa 1996; NTSC Standard; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11740)
    - Breast Cancer: Adjuvant Therapy, 42 year old, 2 positive, 1992 May 15; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11741)
    - 2003 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund, Blair House, 2003 October 22; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 41 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15144)
      Access copy available.
      Scope and Contents
      Focuses on innovations in hospitals and health care delivery system.
    - 2003 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund, Crystal Ballroom - Tape 1, 2003 October 23; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 93 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15145)
      Covers improving the quality of care through innovations in hospitals and health care delivery systems. Topics include waiting lists, nursing shortages, emergency care, improving care coordination among cancer patients, diabetes care, and disease management in Germany.
    - 2003 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund, Crystal Ballroom - Tape 2, 2003 October 23; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 92 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15146)
      Continuation of the International Symposium on health-care policy.
    - 2003 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund, Crystal Ballroom - Tape 3, 2003 October 23; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 92 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15147)
    - 2003 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund, Crystal Ballroom - Tape 4, 2003 October 23; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 91 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15148)
    - 2003 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund, Crystal Ballroom - Tape 5, 2003 October 23; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 45 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15149)
    - 2003 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund - Lunch, 2003 October 23; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 41 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15150)
      Comparing the National Health Service (England) and Kaiser (California) and are there lessons to be learned.
    - 2003 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund, Chandelier Room - Tape 1, 2003 October 23; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 65 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15151)
      Lecture by David Naylor on severe acute respiratory syndrome (SARS) coronavirus.
    - 2003 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund, Crystal Ballroom - Tape 1, 2003 October 24; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 90 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15152)
      The future of hospital care considering the changing patterns of disease and the changing nature of healthcare offerings.
    - 2003 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund, Crystal Ballroom - Tape 2, 2003 October 24; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 94 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15153)
      Topics include quality of care in German hospitals versus ambulatory care, care for individuals with chronic illness, sickness funds, and disease management programs.
    - 2003 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund, Crystal Ballroom - Tape 3, 2003 October 24; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 25 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15154)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - 2001 Commonwealth Fund - Tape 1, 2001 October; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 95 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15155)
      Harvard School of Public Health and the Commonwealth fund talk about a survey that was conducted on attitudes in the five countries towards quality of care prior to September 11th.
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - 2001 Commonwealth Fund - Tape 2, 2001 October; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 92 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15156)
      Topics include: health as active diplomacy, disease eradication, health as politics in the wake of the September 11 (9/11) attacks.
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - 2001 Commonwealth Fund - Tape 3, 2001 October; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 95 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15157)
      "Th Cost of Constraint: The prospects for helathcare reform in Canada," followed by remarks by Senator Michael J. L. Kirby.
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - 2001 Commonwealth Fund - Tape 4, 2001 October; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 94 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15158)
      Discussion on forms of self-care and self-management of diseases like diabetes and rheumatoid arthritis. Approximately 20 minutes into the audio, Peter Smith presents on performance management in the United Kingdom (UK).
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - 2001 Commonwealth Fund - Tape 5, 2001 October; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 95 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 15159)
      A focus on strategies to improve access and quality for at-risk populations. Presentations by Ronald J. Anderson and others on community-oriented primary care programs and improving care for low-income and vulnerable populations.
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - 2001 Commonwealth Fund - Tape 6, 2001 October; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15160)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - 2001 Commonwealth Fund - Tape 7, 2001 October; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15161)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund, 2001 October 9; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15162)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - The Commonwealth Fund, Dinner, Speech, The Chandelier Room, 2001 October 10; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15163)
    - 2002 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Inaugural, John M. Eisenberg, M.D. - Governance, Accountability and Public Input: A New Way to Organize Canada's Health Care System, 2002 October 24; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15164)
    - 2002 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Blair House, Reception-Dinner, Secretary Thompson, Health Minister, 2002 October 23; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15165)
    - International Symposium on Health Care Policy (1), 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15166)
    - International Symposium on Health Care Policy (2), 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15167)
    - International Symposium on Health Care Policy (3), 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15168)
    - International Symposium on Health Care Policy (4), 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15169)
    - International Symposium on Health Care Policy (5), 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15170)
    - International Symposium on Health Care Policy (6), 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15171)
    - International Symposium on Health Care Policy (7), 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15172)
    - International Symposium on Health Care Policy (8), 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15173)
    - International Symposium on Health Care Policy (9), 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15174)
    - International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Day 2 (1), 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15175)
    - International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Day 2 (2), 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15176)
    - International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Day 2 (3), 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15177)
    - International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Day 2 (4), 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15178)
      Access copy currently available.
    - International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Day 2 (5), 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15179)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund - Dinner, 1999 October 20; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15180)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Blair House, Washington, D. C. - Tape 1 of 1, 1999 October 20; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15181)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - St. Regis Hotel, Washington, D. C. - Tape 1 of 8, 1999 October 21; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15182)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - St. Regis Hotel, Washington, D. C. - Tape 2 of 8, 1999 October 21; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AC 15183)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - St. Regis Hotel, Washington, D. C. - Tape 3 of 8, 1999 October 21; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15184)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - St. Regis Hotel, Washington, D. C. - Tape 4 of 8, 1999 October 21; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15185)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - St. Regis Hotel, Washington, D. C. - Tape 5 of 8, 1999 October 22; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15186)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - St. Regis Hotel, Washington, D. C. - Tape 6 of 8, 1999 October 22; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15187)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - St. Regis Hotel, Washington, D. C. - Tape 7 of 8, 1999 October 22; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15188)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - St. Regis Hotel, Washington, D. C. - Tape 8 of 8, 1999 October 22; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15189)
    - 2000 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund, Blair House, No. 1, 2000 October 11; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15190)
    - 2000 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund, News Briefing, Presentations, No. 2, 2000 October 12; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15191)
    - 2000 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - 10AM-12PM Discussion, St. Regis, Crystal Ballroom, No. 3, 2000 October 12; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15192)
    - 2000 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - The Commonwealth Fund - Lunch Speaker, Donald Berwick, No. 4, 2000 October 12; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15193)
    - 2000 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - St. Regis, Crystal Ballroom, Panel I, 1:30 to 3PM, No. 5, 2000 October 12; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15194)
    - 2000 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Panel II, St. Regis, Afternoon, No. 6, 2000 October 12; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15195)
    - 2000 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - St. Regis, Panel III Discussion, 4:50 PM, No. 7, 2000 October 12; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15196)
    - 2000 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - 7:30PM, U. Reinhardt, No. 8, 2000 October 12; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15197)
    - 2000 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund, Friday, October 13, First Session, 9-10:30am, No. 9, 2000 October 13; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15198)
    - 2000 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Commonwealth Fund, Friday, October 13, Second Session, 11-12:30, No. 10, 2000 October 13; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15199)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Tape 1, 2002 June 4; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15200)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Tape 2, 2002 June 4; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15201)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Day 2 - Tape 1, 2002 June 5; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15202)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Day 2 - Tape 2, 2002 June 5; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15203)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Day 2 - Tape 3, 2002 June 5; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15204)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Tape 1 (Tuesday), 2002 January 8; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15205)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Tape 2 (Tuesday), 2002 January 8; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15206)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Wednesday - Tape 2, 2002 January 9; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15207)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Wednesday - Tape 3, 2002 January 9; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15208)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Wednesday - Tape 4, 2002 January 9; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15209)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Wednesday - Tape 5, 2002 January 9; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15210)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Wednesday - Tape 6, 2002 January 9; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15211)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - July 18, 2000, No. 1, No. 2, 2000 July 18; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15212)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - July 18, 2000, No. 3, No. 4, 2000 July 18; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15213)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - July 18, 2000, No. 5, No. 6, 2000 July 18; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15214)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - July 18, 2000, No. 7, No. 8, 2000 July 18; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15215)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Dinner, at Mark Hotel, 2000 July 17; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15216)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Tape 1, 2001 June 26; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15217)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Commonwealth Fund Meeting, Tape 4, 2001 June 26; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15218)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Technical Committee Meeting, 2001 June 26; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15219)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Technical Committee Meeting Tape 2, 2001 June 26; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15220)
    - Unidentified - 1, 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15221)
    - Unidentified - 2, 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15222)
    - Unidentified - 3, 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15223)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting - No. 1, 1999 March 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15224)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting - No. 2, 1999 March 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15225)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting - No. 3, 1999 March 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15226)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting - No. 4, 1999 March 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15227)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting - No. 1, 2002 September 17; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15228)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting - No. 2, 2002 September 17; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15229)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting, 2002 September 18; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15230)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting, 2002 September 18; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15231)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting, 2002 September 18; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15232)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting, 2002 September 18; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15233)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting - Tape 1, 2003 October 1; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15234)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting - Tape 2, 2003 October 1; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15235)